[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
And as part of using this data set,
为了使用这个数据集
the first thing that we're gonna do, just like in the module,
在本模块 我们首先要一如既往地
we're going to build a word-count vector.
建立一个单词统计向量
Build the word count vector for each review.
为每条评论建立单词统计向量
Now, normally, you'd have to implement this and explain something that goes
通常这需要你自己来实现
review, separates words, called tokenizing, build the count vector.
把整条评论变成分开的词 这个过程叫分词 然后再建立统计向量
But one of the nice things about using the tools here in this
但本课程用的工具有一点好处
course is that with just one command, we can build that word count vector.
就是只需要一个命令 我们就能建立单词统计向量
So in products, I'm going to add a new column
我要在products里面新增一列
called word_count, which is gonna start my word count.
这一列叫做word_count 将用来进行单词统计
And if you just call graphlab.text_analytics,
如果你调用graphlab.text_analytics
it's a text analytics toolbox for a bunch of functions,
这个文本分析工具能提供很多函数
there is one called count_words.
其中有一个叫count_words的函数
Notice there's also one called count_ngrams if you wanna use bi-grams,
注意到还有一个叫count_ngrams 如果你想使用bi-grams
tri-grams and so on.
tri-grams等等
And as input, I'm going to give the same products as frame,
我还是用同样产品数据为框架作为输入
but I'm going to ask it to count the words in the review column.
但是让它对评论这一列进行单词统计
And so we're gonna execute that and it's done.
然后我们执行这个命令 它已经执行完毕了
And so now, if we take another look
现在我们再来看这个数据表products
at the products table, so at the head of the table you'll
注意看表的开头部分
see that now we have a fourth column with the word_count.
看现在有了第四列word_count
So we're gonna explore that a little bit more soon.
我们即将会进一步探索它
But you see, for this first review, include the word and
但眼下你可以看到 这第一条评论包含5个and (并且)
five times, stink once.
还有一个stink (烂透了)
Probably that's why it wasn't a good products review, but there's others.
也许这就是这个产品评价不怎么好的原因 但后面还有别的
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community